uh if you're just tuning in this
political vigilante I'm here with John
Kiriakou ex CIA agent
I want to talk now I've covered the the
Epstein case and there's obviously I've
talked to several people say there's
clearly ties with Mossad with the CIA
and this global sex trafficking ring of
like I don't know ruling elites it
sounds pretty horrifying and spreads
pretty wide your experience with the CIA
what do you what do you think of this i
mean i don't i first of all i don't
think he killed himself at all i think i
think either they somebody killed him
one of the powerful people thats in his
black book or the CIA extracted him i
don't know what do you think the day
that he died friend of mine called me
and he said this has to be israelis
right and i said that was the first
thing that came to my mind this has to
be the israelis I'll give the israelis
credit they are really really good spies
really good you know my first week in
the CIA we had a briefing by the
director of security and he gave a talk
about counterintelligence that is
foreign countries having spies in the
united states now we have liaison
relationships with dozens and dozens of
countries and there was called declared
where they come to the united states a
working their country's embassy in
washington and they are declared to the
CIA as intelligence officers so an
israeli embassy in washington there's a
Mossad officer and there's a shittin
back officer and they officially do
liaison with the intelligence community
but the security director told us there
are those two declared Israeli officers
the FBI has been able to identify 187
undeclared Israeli intelligence officers
all around the United States stealing
secrets every single day one of the
things that the Israelis are really good
at it is influence operations now in
part is because they have a natural
constituency in many
Jewish Americans or evangelical
Christians who are pro Israel they are
predisposed to helping Israel in the
first place but that's not always good
enough especially if you're an
intelligence service so what a good
intelligence service would do would be
to sit with your operations officers
around the table and say how do we get
to the very top of the pyramid in this
country to the very top of the political
leadership we need an access agent so
who is out there who knows presidents of
both parties cabinet members of both
parties members of Congress prominent
bankers people in entertainment how
about this guy Jeffrey Epstein
so we can fund him we can finance him we
can introduce him to some business
opportunities to make sure that he has
an income that's great enough that he
doesn't have to just rely on us but we
recruit him and we get him to introduce
us or to give us access to all of these
important people when you look at
Jeffrey Epstein's black book and these
people don't get any more important
you've got the Clintons you have the
trumps you have Prince what's-his-face
from the UK you've got leaders in
entertainment and business and banking
and investments and real estate I mean
everybody who's anybody was in that
black book that's an intelligence
goldmine
that puts whoever recruited him right at
the seat of power so who would have
organization would have the wherewithal
to do something like that
the Russians are good but they're not
that good the Chinese aren't interested
in that kind of thing all they care
about is Science and Technology and for
all intents and purposes that really
only leaves the Israelis so I believe
from the very beginning this was an
Israeli intelligence operation and it
went bad and it went bad because he was
a deeply flawed individual he was a
pedophile and he was a sex addict and he
had he had
hey of just getting himself in trouble
no you can get yourself out of trouble
once maybe he did and whatever it was
2006 but he just couldn't stop he
couldn't stop himself and got in over
his head
so that's fascinating to me so so we
know from victims of him and you know
testimony and all this that one of the
things he would even brag about is you
know is his sort of his modus his MO was
you know bring some wealthy powerful guy
to one of his mansions the butler would
say would you like a massage from a
beautiful young woman she would be a
child they you know they would have sex
and he would have video on this and he
would have leverage on the person like
he was a deliberately gathering leverage
on people which first of all who is he
getting that leverage for you seem to
think it's Mossad and secondly where is
all of all this informations been seized
apparently where is yes and why is the
media now just you know julene maxwell's
still referred to as a socialite in his
gal-pal rather than a pedophile sex
trafficker so yes how do you assess all
of that you are absolutely right I don't
want to sound too too cynical but it
seems to me that because this thing
reached up to the very top I hear that
the fix is in you would think in any
other circumstance every reporter in
America would want a piece of this story
because imagine the Titans that you
could bring down with evidence like this
and I'm not really seeing that you know
we see a couple of fleeting references
now in The Washington Post the New York
Times and if you want a little bit more
detail you have to go to Rolling Stone
Gizmodo or salon.com or whatever that
shouldn't be the case the whole country
should be seized with this story because
I think grave crimes were committed here
and and the media is not covering it
yeah cuz it was a global so it wasn't
just like some single it was like oh it
was Penn State University or this one
Catholic Church or or it's this is the
whole plan I mean this is leaders from
all these powerful country
the royal family the Saudis Israel the
US like you say presidents on both sides
of the aisle bankers all these people
and it is just quietly you know William
bar is focusing on all these bumbling
guards at the prison who fell asleep and
the camera just happened to be unplugged
I mean it just sounds like a joke yeah
yeah it's joke in which I said I didn't
believe that he committed suicide or if
he did he was actively encouraged and
perhaps helped to commit suicide but for
this to have been a legitimate suicide
literally everything every step of the
way would have had to have gone wrong so
do we really believe that the cameras
just happen to be not working or the
guards just happen to be exhausted from
too much overtime and didn't do their
rounds or he just happened to have been
taken out of suicide watch a couple of
days earlier or his cell phone just
happened to be transferred out the day
before and he was literally the only guy
in the prison alone in the cell right
you know MCC Manhattan is not a normal
prison it's a it's a transportation hub
and it's meant not to permanently house
prisoners but to house them only long
enough for them to go on trial or be
transferred to another prison so there's
constant movement in and out constantly
of prisoners if anything there are too
many people in yourself you never find
yourself as the only person in a Cell
but he did and we're supposed to just
take their word for that it was just a
coincidence yeah so obviously but you
you look at that and you don't think the
CIA was involved in this you know the
CIA and I don't think they're smart
enough to be able to pull something like
this off and the thing is you know the
CIA when it really comes down to it the
CIA's real mission is to collect foreign
intelligence they just don't and can't
target Americans like that that they got
caught doing it in the 70s and and they
paid a heavy price
this has
Foreign Intelligence Service and I think
the Israelis the only ones good enough
to do it okay well let's talk a little
bit more now you you made a hypothetical
statement or you said and you can
explain this better than I can we talk -
sure before we started recording about
would the CIA be capable of getting
children for people just to get leverage
on somebody and stuff right can you can
you you made a statement and can you may
discuss that yeah two years ago I gave a
speech at a at a peace conference at
American University it was a speech
about ethics ethics and intelligence
operations and my main point was if you
are a CIA officer or you want to become
on the CIA officer you have to enter
into a job with your own personal set of
morals and ethics because ethics are not
taught ever in under any circumstances
there are no training courses that are
going to teach you right from wrong or
what's and what's not and so as part of
the speech I asked a hypothetical
question
I said let's say you're a CIA case
officer an Operations Officer and you've
recruited a penetration of a foreign
terrorist group whatever you want and
you're you meet with this source every
month in a hotel somewhere in the Middle
East and this guy has proven to be the
real deal right he's giving you
actionable information that you have
used to disrupt attacks and save lives
so you know that this guy is the real
McCoy you vetted him and he he always
tells you the truth so you go to with
him one night in Kyllo let's say and he
says to you look I've been good to you I
give you everything you asked for
I always tell you the truth now you're
going to do something for me you're
going to go out you're gonna get me a
prostitute I say let me see you show of
hands how many people would actually go
out there and get him a prostitute and
usually about three-quarters maybe 80%
put their hands up and I say the answer
is yes you would go out and you would
get him a prostitute
it's not nice
kind of scumbag eree but your job is to
deal with scumbags like this it's for
the good of the country you would go out
and get him across - what if he asks you
for a child prostitute and everybody
kind of you know gasps maybe once in a
while somebody will gingerly put his
hand up and I say absolutely not
not under any circumstances this is a
child for God's sake
I said if you don't know right from
wrong at this point in life then you're
a sociopath and you need to find a
different line of work
the problem though is that nobody's
going to tell you no nobody's gonna say
you know what that's not cool we've got
to draw the line somewhere nobody's
gonna say that because they want the
information they want the recruitments
your job is to break the law anyway
you're not doing it in the United States
yeah it's a terrible world we live in
but you know blah blah blah but the
answer is no not under any circumstances
and then somebody in the audience for
whatever reason ran who confirmed the
CIA prepares children for their sources
right so and it's not all right good
yeah you didn't you didn't say that but
you're saying it's within the realm of
possibility that it has happened because
there's nobody's going hey stop correct
yes it's within the realm of possibility
now we know that this kind of thing
happens we know that because in the
former Yugoslavia a group of contractors
from DynCorp I think it was was arrested
along with several United Nations
officials for doing exactly that for
trafficking in children we know that
it's happening in Somalia Sudan so yeah
they're they're bad people out there
trafficking in children and in you know
a modern-day slave trade really so how
much cuz DynCorp has definitely come up
with with ties to Jeffrey Epstein I mean
do you think that there have been CIA
that have done this with
in some way with Jeffrey Epstein and any
of the people that he's clearly gone
after to try to get leverage I haven't
heard that it would be highly unusual
for a CIA officer to be involved with an
American citizen likes everything I've
seen if Jeffrey Epstein were had been
recruited by an American intelligence
organization or a law enforcement it
would be the FBI the CIA is prohibited
by law from operating operationally in
the United States they they seen
everything to the FBI so that's possible
but unlikely because the FBI they all
have sticks up their ass about you know
following the law that's why I believe
this was the Israelis because these
really care about US law just like we
break the law overseas they break the
law here in the United States and I
think that if they believed that that
would get the information or proximity
to a target especially our president I
think they would do it what do you think
about Jolin Maxwell who his father was
like with Mossad I mean I mean how much
more perfect did that possibly be right
you know there's there's so much smoke
here that there has to be some fire I
want to come back to something that used
to why are you still walking around
having lunch you know at in-n-out burger
on the CIA
why isn't she behind bars or sitting in
a chair in front of a grand jury I don't
understand this at all yeah what did you
think what did you make of that that
that that and some people say oh that
photo was staged it was photoshopped do
they shot it ahead of time but whatever
it was sending a message she's sitting
oh yeah
with this smug smile reading a CIA book
I mean what yes that is that saying haha
CIA Mossad wins or what did what was
that yeah I think that was a slap at the
I think that was a slap of the federal
government she clearly did that on
purpose I don't think I think it was a
legitimate photo that she had staged and
and I think she did it as just a big
middle finger to to the whole USG Wow
well yeah well and you know who has to
do something like
if I was facing human trafficking
charges I wouldn't go protected I think
we need to get to the bottom of that -
how do we do this I mean because as
we've talked about they've sort of the
the press is sort of waned from it
because who knows now me you know CEOs
of media corporations are in his black
book and they're telling the reporters I
cover it else or or just cover it this
way or we've got William bar who I don't
trust now like how do we get to the
bottom of this when it's like the most
powerful people in the world yeah there
are only barely two groups that that
could possibly get anywhere with this
one obviously is the Justice Department
and like you say we can't trust Bo bar
to do any of this for all we know bill
bar is implicated we don't know and the
other is just really good journalists I
don't think we're gonna find those
journalists at the Washington Post the
New York Times and Wall Street Journal I
think that we're probably gonna have to
look to alternative media you know real
go-getters like like BuzzFeed or or The
Daily Beast or you know people who are
hungry otherwise I think that and I hate
to even say this but I think that a lot
this is just gonna end up being cover up
sadly I think you're right
well John thank you so much for spending
time with us today
virgin people follow you online or read
any information coming out there thanks
yeah I'm on Facebook and Twitter at a
website John Kuryakin calm thanks for
having me all right everybody we'll
check out go to John Kiriakou calm and
also support this show go to
patreon.com/scishow and rock friend calm
slash grandma and you can get all my
tour dates and everything at Grandma
1.com thank you so much for watching and
John thank you for taking time today
thank you
you